Concerts in Fukuoka?
Twice?
Solo concerts?
I've done two solo concerts in the last two tours.
I'm very happy that the first day of this tour will be in Fukuoka again!
What is your favorite food in Fukuoka?
Mentaiko (cod roe).
I want to eat ramen noodles with cod roe!
You have a first time visitor, don't you?
Yes, I do.
What is your favorite ramen?
Tonkotsu ramen.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
Bye bye!
Good morning.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll take this. This will open your eyes, right?
Like this, like this,
Like this? This is what I mean.
I got menbei. I love menbei.
I always buy them in packs of 6, so today I think I'll buy a 12-pack.
Yay!
Yay! My house?
This is so good.
I'm starving.
I'll do my best.
Big and beautiful.
It's not in focus like that. It's embarrassing, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
It's cute.
What's this?
I'm definitely going to have to climb it.
I want to fly on this with ice cream.
That's awesome. I want to see the camera.
Oh, my gosh.
What do you think?
Beautiful.
Beautiful!
What is your favorite Fukuoka food?
Favorite Fukuoka gourmet?
I went to Shin Shin!
I don't usually eat ramen at Shinshin, but after today, I want some!
The only time I eat ramen is when I eat at Shinshin in Fukuoka!
You've never seen Ai-chan eat ramen? You love Shinshin-san?
You sound like you're sick of it.
I eat too much, normally, or not enough.
No, you're already eating. We're eating pretty much the same.
Ramen room? I eat as much as the assistant manager outside.
I'll act it out!
I'm conscious of aligning them because Ozora is still scattered down there.
I think a lot of people are bullying him quite a bit.
Okay, 4 minutes.
Get ready.
Four minutes.
Is there anything in there?
Is it in? Are you okay?
Be really careful and don't hurt yourself.
And don't get this one from Umagaeba.
Oh, did I mention that?
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, thank you.
Last, but not least.
It's important.
You can do it if you can just get it together at the end.
Thank you.
And there are some more people up there,
So, the people in the front row are pretty close,
I'm afraid that the people in the front might be distracted by them,
But let's do our best to bring them all in,
Let's do our best to bring the whole audience to the back of the room.
Finally, the show is about to begin.
It's about to start,
I'm really happy to be able to start the tour with all 12 of us together,
I am really happy more than anything else,
I am so thankful for the production,
I am so thankful and grateful for the opportunity to be a part of this tour,
I am so grateful for the opportunity to have this production, and I hope that we can all enjoy it together again,
If we enjoy it the most,
If we enjoy it the most, I think the audience will follow us,
Let's enjoy it to the fullest.
So let's enjoy it to the fullest.
Okay, let's go.
Ready.
Cacone, up!
Good work.
I'm scared. I'm nervous. I don't know what to do.
I can't go.
Take it easy.
Don't push yourself.
It's number 35.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Please take care of me.
Hey, it's a little early.
Microphone.
Everyone, if you can hold a microphone, please hold it.
Thank you very much. I'll do my best.
Mike.
What?
The big carriage should be playing from the 30th minute.
I love it.
Let's do it. Let's do it.
I'm weak.
Sensei?
O-chan.
At the dance.
Always playing in the black.
Ever since sweet Cee Lo opened.
Mr. Lemon Blue took my turn
I'll hit the feeling
I think she already did.
I don't know. I don't know.
What if this is...
If this is...
If this is what love is
It's painful
In my own way
I want to protect you
When you grow up
No matter what happens
We'll be together
For the first time.
You're gonna fall in love.
I'll fall in love with you
Here we go!
All right, everybody, this is the best
It's the best opening of the day. - It's the best opening of the day.
The opening.
In the sky
Stone in the sky
Something good
Cosmetics
8:00 in the morning
let it fall
Which way?
I'll try to take it away
Flowers in the wind
Today too
It's too bright
Lately I've been wishing a lot
Closer to this road
To this mountain
And start to grow
And you
I can't stop shaking
Happiness
If that's what you mean
Now you are for me
I wanted to protect you
I can't hear your voice
It's all I've got
It's the best thing in the world.
If this, if this
If this isn't love
If it's not love
Not this kind of love
I'm not in love with you, you're not in love with me
If you're not in love
Don't be in love with me
Because I'm in love with you
Even if you could walk, I don't want to see you now
I want to think of you all the time
Joy, love, love, love
Love, love, love, love...
The power of love
I want to keep looking at you
I believe in you more
You know what?
You love someone else, but you're not there?
Tell me.
If you don't believe in fate...
Chubba-chubba-chubba-chubba.
Always.
It's always dispirical.
To you and me.
The two I blanked out.
But you know what?
It's a first.
I can't believe it's always the first time.
The lights...
It's over.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
You're not dreaming.
Please don't do this.
Oh, God.
Love is...
Love.
Love
Love is
Heat
Love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love is love
Tangela
Love is love iffe
Tired
Love is
A
iga
Why would I have hated to go back to this dream, these clouds, etc.
Because I still tried to go on
You know you so far away
The clear sky, the light that burned
The sky is full of memories
The clouds hide the town that's grown so small
I'll come back when my dreams come true
Aeon Election
Thank you very much.
It's over?
It's over for the day and night, isn't it?
Thank you very much. It was fun.
I love Fukuoka.
It was fun.
The best Fukuoka.
It's over.
Yay!
Thank you for your hard work.
You're looking good, aren't you?
The first day of the Goal Tour 2024, "From Today You're My Lover," ended in Fukuoka.
The day and night went by so fast.
I was sandwiched between the people of Fukuoka.
It was fun for me to be in Fukuoka, too.
Fukuoka school style.
How was it?
It was the first day, the first time, and there were a lot of first performances.
It was my first hall tour, my first time, and my first time, so I was very nervous.
I was so nervous before the show.
But once the show started, it was a lot of fun.
I was so nervous before the show, but once it started, it was a lot of fun, and it all happened so fast, thanks to you all.
Thanks to all of you
Thanks to all of you, we were able to have a fun live performance.
I'll go to you after the show.
Zabirah is also my boo-boo... she's so nervous...
Not really.
We didn't have time to get together, so I was really nervous,
But today, we're just going to enjoy it.
I was not too hardened, and my goal was to have fun with the fans, and I achieved it.
Enjoyment is the best.
Enjoying it is the best. I am very grateful that the last tour was held on the first day in Fukuoka and this tour will be held on the first day in Fukuoka as well.
I was very excited about PHT and Peach Pie, too,
The coupling of the last tour was also very cute and dreamy, so I did my best with a lot of excitement.
I did my best to be cute.
Last time, right?
Really, last time.
So I was really happy to hear that it was the first time for me to perform on the first day,
And the noon show was a complete first for me, so the video was a bit...coupled...
The video was like a coupling... Kachiro, and then the song was performed, so I could hear the cheers of the fans, even though I was wearing an ear monitors,
I was so happy to hear their voices and their penlights.
I am really looking forward to the next shows in Hyogo, Osaka, Chiba, and so on.
I'm really looking forward to Hyogo, Osaka, Chiba, and so on.
I'm sure it will be over in the blink of an eye.
I know it will be over in the blink of an eye, but today really flew by, so let's just chew it up.
The next one will be in Hyogo in no time...
Kobe is at the end of this month, so let's do our best, senpai.
Well, I'll do my best in Kobe!
I'll do my best in Kobe!
I'll do my best!